{
    "id": "3cff72780a984c3c9df1b492939df57d",
    "title": "Too, Enough and Soâ€¦That",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "77a83605f9974bfd844d6bbc860d0168",
            "title": "Too, Enough, and So...That",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She wasn't .......................... to be discouraged by some of her teachers.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too weak",
                        "weak enough",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She soon grew ......................... to manage without a hearing aid.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so deaf",
                        "too deaf",
                        "deaf enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The task was ............................ for any teenager fresh from a Scottish farm.",
                    "description": "Enough is an adverb. It goes after the adjective or adverb modified by it. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough daunting",
                        "daunting enough",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Rahul was .......................... busy that he could not talk to me.",
                    "description": "Note the pattern 'so....that'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "so",
                        "enough",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The car is ........................... to seat six people.",
                    "description": "The expression 'too large' has a negative meaning. 'Large enough' shows adequacy. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "too large",
                        "so large",
                        "large enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He walked ............................ fast that I could not catch up with him.",
                    "description": "Note the pattern 'so...that'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "so",
                        "enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ............................ to buy a car.",
                    "description": "When enough is used as an adverb, it goes after the adjective or adverb modified by it.  The expression 'rich enough' has a positive meaning whereas the expression 'too rich' has a negative meaning. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough rich",
                        "rich enough",
                        "too rich"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was ......................... proud to apologize.",
                    "description": "Note the pattern 'too...to'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "so",
                        "enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "None of the mangoes is .............................. to be eaten.",
                    "description": "Enough goes after the adjective modified by it. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "ripe enough",
                        "enough ripe",
                        "so ripe"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has ............................. many students in her class that she cannot give them individual attention.",
                    "description": "Note the pattern 'so...that'. We cannot use a that-clause after very.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "so",
                        "very"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is ................................ to solve the problem.",
                    "description": "The expression 'intelligent enough' has a positive meaning whereas the expression 'too intelligent' has a negative meaning. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough intelligent",
                        "intelligent enough",
                        "too intelligent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The light was not .............................. for one to see things clearly.",
                    "description": "'Bright enough' has a positive meaning. It shows adequacy. 'Too bright' has a negative meaning. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough bright",
                        "bright enough",
                        "too bright",
                        "very bright"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}